<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACMI</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on ACMI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Download</title><link>/usage/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/usage/download/</guid><description>Download the latest release to somewhere convenient on your computer (put it with your packing scripts if you&amp;rsquo;re using them).
ACMI won't update itself at this time. Make sure to check [releases](https://github.com/agc93/acmi/releases) regularly for new updates.</description></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>/usage/usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/usage/usage/</guid><description>If your mods are in your current directory, just run acmi.exe build to build the installer files, or you can pass a specific directory like acmi.exe build D:/Mods/MyAwesomeSkinPack if it&amp;rsquo;s not in the current directory. You can also just drag-and-drop your mod folder onto the acmi.exe file (see the Walkthrough below) to immediately build installer files for that directory.
If it completes successfully, you should see a new fomod directory in your mod files.</description></item><item><title>Images</title><link>/extras/images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/extras/images/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll try our best to find a suitable image for the installer as a whole. This will be shown on the first page of the installer and for any steps without their own images. If there&amp;rsquo;s only one .png/.jpg in the root folder, we&amp;rsquo;ll use that. If there&amp;rsquo;s more than one, we&amp;rsquo;ll use the first one we find with &amp;ldquo;preview&amp;rdquo; in the name.
You can also have images for your individual skin files!</description></item><item><title>Multi-Skin Files</title><link>/extras/merged/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/extras/merged/</guid><description>If your mod directory includes .pak files with more than one skin in them (such as merged NPC files), include the exact string MULTI anywhere in the file name. This tells ACMI to scan a much larger chunk of the file to find skins and include any it finds, not just the first one.
This can slow down the build process quite a bit if you have lots of large merged files, but your installer will be misleading if you don't.</description></item></channel></rss>