<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Extras/Advanced on ACMI</title><link>/installer/extras/</link><description>Recent content in Extras/Advanced on ACMI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-au</language><atom:link href="/installer/extras/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Images</title><link>/installer/extras/images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installer/extras/images/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll try our best to find a suitable image for the installer as a whole. This will be shown on the first page of the installer and for any steps without their own images. If there&amp;rsquo;s only one .png/.jpg in the root folder, we&amp;rsquo;ll use that. If there&amp;rsquo;s more than one, we&amp;rsquo;ll use the first one we find with &amp;ldquo;preview&amp;rdquo; in the name.
You can also have images for your individual skin files!</description></item><item><title>Multi-Skin Files</title><link>/installer/extras/merged/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installer/extras/merged/</guid><description>If your mod directory includes .pak files with more than one skin in them (such as merged NPC files), include the exact string MULTI anywhere in the file name. This tells ACMI to scan a much larger chunk of the file to find skins and include any it finds, not just the first one.
This can slow down the build process quite a bit if you have lots of large merged files, but your installer will be misleading if you don't.</description></item><item><title>Special Files</title><link>/installer/extras/special/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installer/extras/special/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a couple of things you can also do to tweak how ACMI picks up your files and includes them in an installer.
Lightweight Packing If the mod has been packed using Cherry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;lightweight&amp;rdquo; packing method, the individual slot files will have nothing but an instance file in them so ACMI won&amp;rsquo;t detect them as a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; skin file. If you include (LIGHT) or (LW) somewhere in the file name, ACMI will instead detect those instance files and sort them into planes and slots correctly.</description></item></channel></rss>